const QuizData = [
    {"question":"I ______ tennis every Sunday morning.","correct_value":2,"answers":["plays","play","am playing","am play"]},
    {"question":"John ______ his teeth before breakfast every morning.","correct_value":3,"answers":["clean","cleaning","cleans","is cleaning"]},
    {"question":"Sorry, she can't come to the phone. She _______ a bath.","correct_value":1,"answers":["is having","having","have","has"]},
    {"question":"It _____ many times every winter in Frankfurt.","correct_value":1,"answers":["snows","snowing","is snowing","is snow"]},
    {"question":"How many students in your class _____ from Korea?","correct_value":2,"answers":["comes","come","came","are coming"]},
    {"question":"Babies _____ when they are hungry.","correct_value":4,"answers":["crying","are crying","cries","cry"]},
    {"question":"I ______ for my pen. Have you seen it?","correct_value":1,"answers":["am looking","look","looking","will look"]},
    {"question":"The phone _____ Can you answer it, please?","correct_value":3,"answers":["rings","was ringing","is ringing","will ring"]},
    {"question":"You can keep my iPod if you like. I _____ it any more.","correct_value":2,"answers":["doesn't use","don't use","didn't use","am not using"]},
    {"question":"Sorry, you can't borrow my pencil. I _____ it myself.","correct_value":4,"answers":["was using","use","used","am using"]}
];
export default QuizData;